人人影视
YYeTs.com
本字幕由人人影视字幕组翻译
禁止用作任何商业盈利行为
翻译： 暴龙蛋    圈圈    阿髻    Roaddog
翻译： 苏小黛    Kiko    DustD    胖兔纯
时间轴： 浓子   萌    校对： 苏小黛   胖兔纯
后期： 孤帆    总监： 米小勒   胖兔纯
塞勒姆
第一季  第七集
《塞勒姆》前情提要
Previously on "Salem".
私通者
Fornicator!
他调查了一番
He searches.
巫师到底在哪里
So where is the witch?
就在这里
Right here.
如果他势不可挡
If he cannot be stopped,
游戏就又有得玩了  不是吗
well, then it's an entirely new game, isn't it?
你父亲所做的一切都是为了你
Everything your father does, he does for you.
我不再满足于只做你的顾客了
I no longer want to be your customer.
真爱无价
True love cannot be bought or sold.
让我们为自己而活
Let's just live.
你仍然爱着约翰·奥登
You still love John Alden.
大祭典要酝酿在没有情感的心里才是最佳
The grand rite ferments best in a loveless heart.
它只听从我的吩咐
He serves at my behest.
你是没法让它出来的
He won't come out for you.
父亲
Father.
亲爱的英克里斯
My dear Increase.
不知此次您会在镇上停留多久呢
How long may we enjoy your presence in town?
直到我见证那些恶魔的妓女
Until every last devil's whore of a witch
塞勒姆最后一个巫师死去
in Salem is dead.
堕落
Depravity.
还有比这更适合的词儿
Can there be a more apt word
来形容你们城市的现状吗
to describe the current state of your fair city?
烂醉  放荡
Drink, perversity,
一切的一切
abominations of each and every variety
都让人恶心
offered and received.
正是你们迎合内心的恶魔
And even as we cater to our inner demons,
造就了他们的繁荣昌盛
we have allowed actual demons to flourish!
巫师
Witches!
他不应该在这儿的
He was not supposed to be here.
怎么会这样
So why is he?
他来看他儿子的作为
He came to see what his son had accomplished.
那他怎么留下来了
And why is he staying?
他看到了他儿子的作为
He saw what his son had accomplished.
巫师就在我们中间
There are witches hidden amongst us,
而你们这些塞勒姆的人
and you people of Salem,
却沉迷于酒肉
seduced by drink and by flesh,
坐视不理
are happily blinded to it.
我在这里
Standing before you,
以天为证
with the certainty of the rising sun,
我将改变这一切
I assure you this will change.
西布里夫人
Mrs. Sibley.
牧师
Reverend,
您的话振奋人心
your words are inspiration.
您是英格兰的损失  也是我们的福气
England's loss is our gain.
相信您丈夫的情况已有好转
I trust your husband's condition is improving.
很遗憾  没有
Sadly, no.
那麻烦转告乔治
Well, please tell George
我会再去看他的
I shall visit him again at once.
也许我的出现会让他好过一点
Perhaps my presence may be of some comfort to him.
那是自然
Oh, how could it not?
我不知道说什么好了
I have no words.
简直飘然欲仙
Like a man who's seen the face of god.
只有心怀敬畏的沉默才能表达我此刻的心情
Only an awed silence is the appropriate response.
你父亲
Your father.
好好的心情又没了
And like that, the mood is ruined.
不  真是你父亲
No, your... your father.
他跟一群人一起
He's...he's in the common.
当然了  乌泱泱一堆人围着听他废话
With a crowd, no doubt, hanging on his every word.
一堆人没错  但他没说话
With a crowd, yes, but he's not speaking.
那你肯定是看错了
Well, then you must have him confused with someone else.
他正往这来呢
He's walking this way.
什么叫"往这来"
And by "This way," You mean...
不能让他看到我在这
He cannot find me here.
要彻底净化塞勒姆
And where better to begin our cleansing of Salem
就得从这个肮脏的地方开始
than in its most vile den?
后楼梯在哪
The back stairs.
不行  你会经过楼梯平台的
No, no, no, no, y-you'll cross the landing.
格里安娜  我父亲不理解我
Gloriana, my father does not understand me.
他从不理解我
He never has.
-若是他发现我...  -躲床下去
- If he discovers me... - Under the bed now.
-什么  -快躲床下去
- What?! - Under the bed now!
我的圣经呢
Where's my bible?
我没看到啊
I-I-I don't see it!
麦哲牧师
Reverend Mather.
你认识我吗
You know me?
这里谁不认识您啊
Is there anyone in the province who doesn't?
你一个人吗
You are alone?
不
No.
还有我的主
I'm here with my lord.
他的话
His words, anyway.
总能在这个危机四伏的世道中给我安慰
They offer great comfort in these perilous times...
即使是对我这样的女人
Even for a woman like me.
你们没感觉到吗
Do you not sense it?
罪恶和巫术的同流合污
The commingling of sin and sorcery?
深呼吸
Take a breath.
你们就可以感觉到
You can almost taste it...
撒旦剧毒的花蜜
Satan's toxic nectar,
妄图使人放下防备偏离正轨
designed to divert and disarm.
这个美妙之地的老板娘
The proprietress of this charming establishment.
今天要什么样的  牧师
What'll it be today, Reverend?
苗条温顺的
Thin and pliant,
还是丰腴风趣的呢
or thick and playful?
说话注意点  女士
Mind your betters, madam.
我是正经做生意的
I run an honest house.
你不会在这里发现什么的
You'll find nothing here.
我这个人出名就出名在
I have made my name finding things
可以在无物之地发现东西
where there is nothing to be found.
鸢尾根粉
Orris root?
这里每天都有形形色色的人来来往往
Strangers tramp in and out of here every day.
他们带什么东西我怎么知道
I do not know what substances they carry.
施咒石
Casting stones.
塞勒姆的行政委员们
Selectmen of Salem...
我们发现了一个巫师
We've uncovered a witch.
*擂我战鼓*
*Pound me the witch drums*
*鼓鸣震天*
*Witch drums*
*擂我战鼓*
*Pound me the witch drums*
*鼓鸣震天*
*The witch drums*
*宁入地狱*
*Better pray for hell*
*不留人间*
*Not hallelujah*
我们的人被抓了
One of ours.
正是他踏下那艘船后我们日夜担心的事
Exactly what we feared the minute he stepped off that ship.
现在你明白了吧
Now, well, you know what this means.
我不像你一样恐慌
Just because I don't share your panic
并不意味着我不担心此事
doesn't mean I don't grasp the stakes.
他会逼她供出名字
He will press her for names,
你觉得她会供出谁呢
and whose will be she tempted to provide?
她太大意了
She was careless,
竟然把与巫师相关的东西放在身边
leaving objects of her craft so close at hand.
因为她的大意  我们可能都被烧死
And for that carelessness, we may all burn,
更不用说我们的大祭典了
to say nothing of what will become of our grand rite.
你的歇斯底里对事情没有任何帮助
Your hysteria offers no solutions.
我们只是需要提醒一下梅布我们对她的期望
Mab simply needs to be reminded what is expected of her.
她的沉默
Her silence.
说得对
You're right.
我马上去见她
I shall pay her a visit at once.
你很担心
You're worried.
老麦哲  他很难对付
He is formidable, the senior Mather,
他既像恶霸  又像猎狗般的侦探
part bully, part bloodhound.
梅布一直对组织很忠诚
Mab has been loyal to the hive throughout.
我担心的不是梅布
It is not Mab that worries me.
英克里斯说要再来看乔治
Increase promises to pay another visit.
肯定不久之后就会发现
How long before he realizes
他不是生病  而是被施咒了
that George is not sick, but spelled?
那他会怪谁
And at whose hands?
我
Mine.
那就阻止它的发生
Then prevent this.
对
Yes.
英克里斯可以随时过来
Increase may visit at his pleasure,
尽责的妻子怎么会在丈夫需要人照看的时候
for what loving wife would leave her ailing husband at home
将他一个人留在家里呢
when his condition demands attention at once?
你今天怎么这么早就来喝酒
You're drinking early today.
如果你认识我父亲
If you knew my father,
一定会表扬我撑了那么久才来
you'd commend me for waiting this long.
你这话说的好像你父亲...
You know, the way you speak of him, you make him sound --
很没人性对吗
Inhuman?
-对  -这就对了
- Yes. - Good.
这说明我描述得非常形象精确
Then I have painted an accurate picture.
你不信吗  自己看好了
Don't believe me? See for yourself.
柯顿  你都找了你一早上了
Cotton, I've been in search of you all morning.
我是不是早该意识到
I supposed I should have realized
你肯定会在有酒的地方
you would be somewhere where whiskey is served.
父亲  这是约翰
Father, this is John...
约翰·奥登
John Alden.
念大学时我跟你父亲是同班同学
Your father and I were classmates at university.
我知道
Yes, I know.
我很荣幸  上尉
An honor, Captain.
真的  我一向非常敬佩
Truly, I can have no greater respect
上过战场浴血奋战的人
than for a man who has risked his life in battle.
遗憾的是  并非所有人都跟你一样有勇气
Sadly, not all young men possess the same mettle.
你来干什么  父亲
What brings you, Father?
我万万没想到
Well, I am shocked to discover
塞勒姆现在已经腐败堕落到了这种地步
the extent of the depravity and immorality in Salem.
得提醒人们所犯之罪的报应
The people need a reminder of the wages of their sin.
他们会得到提醒的
And so they will get one.
在周日的布道上
In Sunday's sermon.
不  不
No. No.
他们现在就得听到你的声音
They need to hear your voice now.
向平民发表公开演讲
A public recitation on the commons,
以罪恶之脸来例证
illustrated by the face of sin.
罪恶之脸
The face of sin?
那又是谁
And who is that?
柯顿
And Cotton?
你的圣经
Your Bible.
波士顿的医院正等着他
The hospital in Boston awaits him.
他的身体每况愈下
It is my only hope to find a cure
这是治好他最后的办法了
for his worsening condition.
还有  艾萨克
And, Isaac,
因为我丈夫曾对你做过的事
your feelings towards my husband
你对他的恨意
for what he once did...
可以理解
they're understandable,
但在他危急之时施以援手
but to help him in his hour of need
展现出了你真正的价值
shows me the true measure of you...
对此我将永远感激
for which I am forever grateful.
我们拂晓便能抵达波士顿
We will be in Boston by daybreak.
能和囚犯单独聊几句吗
A moment with the accused?
是  治安官
Yes, Magistrate.
你是来杀我的
You've come here to kill me.
我也有权这么做
It would be within my right to do so.
巫师的条文是很明确的
The code of the hive is clear.
但我们已经同意留你一命
But, no, we have agreed to spare you.
我一定会保住你
I would allow nothing else.
不过
Still...
当务之急
to the issue at hand.
他会审问你
He will interrogate you.
我会守口如瓶
And I will give him nothing.
我会在背叛大业之前吞下自尽之药
I will swallow the blackened pill before I betray the cause.
你当然是这么想的
That will be your intent, yes,
但他会折磨你
Until he tortures you
听到你痛苦的哭喊声之后
and then, hearing your cries of pain,
再继续加倍折磨你
tortures you some more,
到时候你就会乞求他
at which point you will beg for him
只要让你免于痛苦折磨
to allow you to offer a name,
你就告诉他同谋的名字
even if only to release yourself from the agony.
这是必然趋势
When that happens...
到那时
and it will happen...
我要你给出一个混淆视听的名字
I have just the distraction for you to provide.
大晚上的您去哪儿了  父亲
Where do you go at night, father?
安  这么晚还没睡吗
Anne. Awake at this hour?
母亲说我不该问这种问题
Mother says I shouldn't ask such questions,
说你为了我们做出牺牲
that I should simply be grateful
我们只要满怀感激就够了
for the sacrifices you make on our behalf.
胡说  想问什么就问
Nonsense. Ask whatever you like.
今晚我在忙镇里的事
Tonight I was preoccupied with business of the town.
你相信她是个巫师吗
And do you believe she is a witch?
谁
Who?
你去监狱见的那个女人
The woman you sought out at the jail.
你跟踪我吗
You followed me?
我只想知道你做出了什么牺牲
I simply wanted to know what those sacrifices were
为什么总要在秘密中进行
and why they seem to be so often made in secret.
你先是窥探我的房间
First you snoop about in my room,
偷翻我的物品  现在又...
unearthing my belongings, and now...
不是
No.
什么不是
No? What?
我不觉得她是巫师
No, I do not believe she is a witch.
她只是个孤苦伶仃的女人罢了
She is but a sad, lonely woman.
我很高兴
I am glad to hear
塞勒姆还有人是通情理的
there is some common sense left in Salem.
晚安  父亲
Good night, father.
晚安  亲爱的
Good night, dear.
水刑场
求求你们  我是无辜的
Please! I am innocent!
你已就施行巫术一事认罪
You have pled guilty to the practice of witchcraft.
但仅仅认罪还不足以赦免你的命
But such a plea is not sufficient to spare your life.
我要其他巫师的名字
I want names of others.
我不认识任何巫师
I know of no others.
再来
Again.
不要  我发誓我是清白的
No! I swear I'm innocent!
他疯了
He's insane.
这还是轻的
On a good day.
唯有说出同谋巫师之名
Only the name of a fellow witch
才能饶你一命
will spare your life.
我不认识其他巫师
I know of no others.
我会再问一次  不过事先警告你
I will ask again, but first a caution.
下一次  海水不仅会灌满你的嘴
The next time, the saltwater that filled your mouth only
还会经由喉咙流进你的肺里
will travel down your throat into your lungs.
你奋力挣扎而品尝到的
And then the taste you struggle to discern
不会是水或空气  而是死亡的味道
will not be of water, nor of air, but of death.
名字
A name.
等等
Wait!
我只等你说出我们之中的巫师
And I wait only for the name of a fellow witch.
我说
And I will give it to you.
她  格里安娜
Her! Gloriana!
不可能
No.
No. No. No!
错了  父亲  一定是错了
This is a mistake. No, father, this is a mistake.
安布里小姐绝非巫师
Miss Embry is no witch.
你只需看  不得插手
You are here to observe, not to interfere.
听我说  父亲
Listen to me, father.
这正是我想告诉你的
This is what I have tried to tell you,
现在看来更明显了
and now I see it to be true
我们错了
that we have been wrong.
柯顿
Cotton.
我们群情激昂铲除族中的撒旦
That in our zeal to rid satan from our midst,
实则是在以此滥杀无辜
we are instead killing innocents.
别指手画脚
Do not presume to instruct me.
我们在协助恶魔为害世间
We are doing the devil's work for him!
那我毕生心血竟是大错吗
And my life's work is a mistake?
无意冒犯  是的
Respectfully... yes.
让开
Stand aside.
求你了  父亲  饶恕她
Please, father, I beg you -- spare her.
让开
Get out of my way.
听我说
Listen to me!
听到了
I have.
我绝不许你再愚蠢行事
And I will no longer let you act the fool.
你确定愚蠢行事的是我吗
You are sure it is I who acts the fool?
柯顿
Cotton.
关她进笼
Take her to the cage.
柯顿  柯顿
Cotton. Cotton!
别
No.
柯顿
Cotton!
上帝啊  怎么了  西布里先生
Oh, lord. What is it, Mr. Sibley?
呼吸就好  西布里先生
Try to breathe, Mr. Sibley. That's it.
慢慢呼吸  西布里先生
Slow breath, Mr. Sibley.
对
That's right.
对  慢慢地
That's it, nice and easy.
不要
No!
父亲
Father!
父亲  你无凭无据
Father, you have no evidence.
一派胡言  已有巫师公然指认了
Nonsense. I have the word of an admitted witch.
一个习练巫术的女人
A woman who practices the devil's craft?
你竟相信她的指认
You trust her to finger others?
告诉我
Tell me...
所有的指责都会让你如此激愤吗
do all accusations stir such passions in you?
还是这个妓女对你别有意义
Or is there something unique about the whore's case?
我了解这里的人
I know these people.
我们一起生活
I have lived among them.
安布里小姐绝非撒旦信众
Miss Embry is no tool of satan.
若她面对恶魔印记的检验会如何
And if she were to be examined for the devil's marks?
检验
An examination?
我相信
I'm confident...
不  我确信您会无功而返
no, I am certain...that you would find nothing.
说实话  我希望您一鼓作气
In fact, yes, I would encourage you to settle the issue
即刻进行验证
and conduct the exam at once.
我
Me?
不
No.
不  我交给你了
No, I will leave that to you.
由你来验证她是否清白
You will examine the accused.
上尉
Captain.
约翰
John!
这可不是我期待的反应
That wasn't the reaction I was expecting.
彼此彼此
Nor the greeting I was.
那晚
The other night...
我们所说之话  所做之事
what we said... what we did.
如何  你后悔了吗
What, do you regret it?
不
No.
我只后悔那是昙花一现
My only regret is that it can never happen again.
我是有夫之妇  约翰
I'm a married woman, John.
丈夫已将油尽灯枯
With a very sick husband.
西布里先生绝不会如我愿辞世的
Mr. Sibley would never do me the favor of dying.
我们都明白
We both know that.
他被带去了医院
He was taken to hospital.
也会痊愈归来
From where he will surely return...
生龙活虎犹如从前
as alive and married as ever.
就因为这个吗
Is that the reason?
西布里
Sibley?
仅此而已吗
Nothing else?
不是因为害怕
Not a fear?
或是什么你觉得我接受不了的秘密
Or a secret that you think I couldn't accept?
塞勒姆没有人
Because there is no one in Salem
能对他们的过去全然无愧
unburdened by their past...
就连我也不行
Not even me.
抱歉  约翰
I'm sorry, John.
希望你能明白
I hope you can understand.
父亲  求你了
Father, please.
开始
Proceed.
没有印记
No marks.
把她翻过来
Turn her.
没有
Nothing.
罩衫掀起来
Raise her smock.
还是没有
Still nothing.
还有上半身
The upper torso.
父亲
Father...
上半身
The upper torso.
等等
Wait.
你看到了  就像我说的
So, you see, as I assured you,
她没有恶魔的印记
She bears no signs of a devil's agent,
没有斑点  没有巫师的乳头
No blemishes, no witches' teats.
这些我都会在审判她时如实提到的
All of which I will be sure to mention at her trial.
审判
Her trial?
我已经向你证明了她没有印记
But I have proven to you she is without marks.
你忘了吗
Have you forgotten?
我们不是评判者
We are not judges.
我们只是寻找真相的人
We are simply seekers of the truth.
结论取决于委员会
The power of verdict rests with the selectmen.
这是塞勒姆  你知道他们会怎么投票
This is Salem. You know how they will vote.
那就把你的怒气和无力留着对付他们吧
Well, then you save your rage and your impudence for them.
如你所见  今天又有一个女人被指控了
Another woman was accused today...as you saw.
这巫师恐慌太疯狂了
It's madness, this witch panic.
确实令人遗憾
Yes, it is regrettable.
令人遗憾
Regrettable?
不然你想让我怎么做
What would you have me do?
你可以站出来  提出抗议
You could speak out, rail against it.
比起袖手旁观  你还有很多别的选择
You have any number of options beyond nothing.
我只是一个人  可能你对我期望太多了
I am one man. Perhaps you expect too much of me.
也可能是你太满足于现状
Perhaps you are content with too little.
注意态度  孩子
Hold your tongue, child.
我只是不明白
I just don't understand
他怎么能忍受看着人们被吊死
Why he's so content to see people hang...
几乎让人觉得他享受这种过程
Almost as if he secretly likes it.
别含沙射影
I don't appreciate the insinuation.
我怎么含沙射影了
What insinuation is that?
你暗指我跟那些
That I was somehow in league
杀人的清教徒是一伙儿的
with the murdering puritans.
不  我绝对不是那个意思
Oh, no, that was not my insinuation at all.
其实恰恰相反
In fact, it was quite the opposite.
什么意思
And what might that be?
我...我突然觉得很累
You know, I'm... I'm suddenly very tired.
你到底想指控我什么
What are you accusing me of?
我想我该去躺一会
I think I should lie down.
安  没解释清楚不准走
Anne, do not walk away until you have explained yourself.
安
Anne!
我能问你个问题吗
May I ask you a question?
他为什么恨你
Why does he hate you?
只有两个原因
Two reasons only...
一是因为我是谁
For what I am...
二是因为我不是谁
And what I am not.
你替那女孩向他求情了
And you've appealed to him on the girl's behalf?
不只一次  他根本听不进去我说的
Repeatedly. He does not regard me.
说实话吧  谁的话他都听不进去  除了...
Truth told, he does not regard anyone except...
除了你  约翰
for you, John.
柯顿  不行
Cotton, no.
你就是他希望我成为的样子
You are everything he ever wished me to be.
你是战争中的英雄
You are a hero in war.
你是个没有弱点的男人
You are a man without weakness or frailty.
柯顿  抱歉
Cotton, I'm sorry.
去求一个清教徒混蛋做正确的事
Begging another puritan asshole to do the right thing?
这什么时候成功过
Since when has it worked?
-现在又怎么可能成功  -你说得对
-And why would it work now? -You're right.
没人应该被逼着向我父亲低头
No man should be forced to humble himself before my father.
我来塞勒姆几个月了
I have been in Salem for months.
结识了不少盟友与敌人
I have made allies and enemies in scores.
但对我来说  最可能称得上朋友的
But the closest thing that I have come to a friend...
就是你
...is you.
所以我请你
So I ask you...
我求你
I beg you...
帮我向父亲求求情
to appeal to my father,
如果在你心中
If there is some small part of you
也曾有一丝将我当做朋友的话
that can call me a friend, too.
西布里先生
Mr. Sibley?
Mr. Sibley?!
西布里先生
Mr. Sibley.
帮我  艾萨克
Help me, Isaac.
你可以说话
You can speak.
这是主神奇的杰作
The lord's miraculous workings.
你在流血
You're leaking blood.
所以我才需要你的帮助
Which is why I need your help.
去塞勒姆
Go to salem.
带着急救药品和懂得施救的人回来
Return with supplies and one to administer them.
帮助你吗
Help you?
是
Yes.
还记得你烙印我的那天吗
Do you remember the day you marked me?
你把私通者印记烙在我血肉上的那天
The day you seared my flesh with the sign of the fornicator?
你记得吗
You remember that?
我能想象从那之后  你一定无时无刻
And I would imagine that not a moment has since passed
都在诅咒着我死去
that you didn't wish me dead.
如今你的机会来了  甚至不需你亲自动手
And now your chance, without even raising a hand.
只要你见死不救  我肯定会死在这里
Walk away, and I will surely die here.
我为什么不
Why shouldn't I?
因为当你一心一意寻求复仇时
Because while you desired revenge
我却饱受悔恨的侵蚀
I bore regret for what I did.
你可真会说
Words.
那就帮助我  我会慷慨待你
Then help me, and I will shower you
不是空口白话  而是黄金
Not with words, but gold,
你无法想象的丰厚酬劳
more than you've ever hoped to possess.
黄金
Gold?
只要我带回来  药品和西布里太太吗
To return with -- with medicines and Mrs. Sibley?
不
No.
别带她
Not her.
英克里斯
Increase.
Increase?
别对我妻子透露一个字
Tell my wife nothing.
马上给我把英克里斯·麦哲带来
Bring me Increase Mather at once.
快去
Go now, boy!
快跑
Run!
跑啊
请进
Yes?
牧师
Reverend.
答案是不行
The answer is no.
我都还没开口呢
I didn't ask a question.
你是来求我放过那个妓女的  是吗
You're here to beg for the whore's life, are you not?
毫无疑问  是我那个愚蠢的儿子请你来的
Dispatched by my besotted son, no doubt.
没错
Yes.
我就跟你直说了吧  奥登上尉
Well, let me save you the trouble, Captain Alden.
我已经决定让她接受审判
The decision has been made to take her to trial.
但是你放心  我会告诉柯顿
But rest assured I will be sure to tell cotton
你的求情十分真挚诚恳
that your pleas were most heartfelt.
先生  格里安娜不是女巫
Sir...Gloriana is no witch.
不
No.
不过我想你也同意她蛊惑了我儿子
But I think you will agree she has bewitched my son.
我父亲非常敬重您  牧师
You know, my father held you in high regard, reverend.
老奥登是个好人
Alden sr. was a good man.
他对这世界总有与众不同的看法
He viewed the world with uncommon reason.
没错  除了看待自己儿子的时候
Yeah, well, except when it came to his own son.
他想要我研究神学
He wanted me to study scripture,
而我却选择探索丛林
and I chose to explore the woods.
他想要我上大学
He wanted me to attend university,
而我却志愿入伍打仗
and I volunteered for war.
他去世时仍认为我的人生抉择是个错误
He went to his grave thinking my life's choices mistakes.
但是他允许我犯下这些错误
And yet he allowed you to make them.
那是因为他了解差别
Well, that's because he knew the difference.
什么差别
Between?
爱他儿子的选择
Between loving his son's choices
还是爱他儿子本人
and loving his son.
奥登上尉
Captain Alden.
艾萨克  怎么了
Isaac, what is it?
别在这儿说
Not here.
乔治·西布里能说话了
George Sibley can speak?
与你我无二异
As clearly as you or I.
身受重伤却不告诉自己的妻子
And wounded, he doesn't request his wife,
-而是求助  -英克里斯·麦哲
- But asks for - Increase Mather.
我对他的信任比小偷还少
I trust him no more than a thief.
但是违背一个他这种身份的人
But to disobey a man of his standing?
什么也别做
Then do nothing.
上尉
Captain?
你征求我的意见  这就是我的建议
You sought my advice, so I offer it.
什么也别做
Do nothing.
但是就那么把他
But to leave him any longer
抛弃在树林里  血流不止
than I have in the woods, bleeding...
他会死
He will die.
没错
Yes.
这不正是他应得的下场吗
Does he deserve anything less?
那人在你身上烙下了印记
The man who marked your flesh...
将我推入战争
drove me to war...
还像疯王一样统治着塞勒姆
and has ruled over salem like a power-mad king?
现在却来乞求怜悯
And now, what, he begs for compassion?
让我们帮助他
Cooperation?
怎么了
What?
我知道你爱她  上尉
I know you love her, captain.
但这样见死不救  是谋杀
But to leave him to die is murder.
什么  都别做
Do...nothing.
不  你要带我去哪
No. Where are you taking me?
告诉我  你要带我去哪
Tell me! Where are you taking me?!
塞勒姆的好人们
Good people of Salem,
我已经注意到
It has come to my attention
今天所提出的指控
that the accusation leveled today
是巫师们的诡计
was a trick of the witches...
阴险的计谋
An infernal ploy
迷惑并让我们忽视了真正的罪恶
to delude and distract from the truly guilty.
这个女人并非女巫
This woman is no sorceress.
因此她无需进行审判
And therefore she will not go to trial.
但支持她的人并未意识到
But what her advocates fail to grasp
没有罪行不代表无辜
is that absence of guilt does not mean innocence...
这名妓女绝不是无辜者
For this whore is no innocent -- far from it.
她罪犯罪恶  淫肉之恶
She is guilty of sin, sins of the flesh,
怒神之恶  凡人与非人之恶并犯
sins against god, sins both mortal and eternal,
因上指责  塞勒姆将无其容身之所
And as such, she warrants no place in Salem.
不
No.
因此  我将下令
And so, by my decree,
她自此被我等驱逐
she is hereby banished from our midst,
驱逐立刻执行  不得争议
her expulsion immediate and beyond dispute.
而如果她  看着我
And should she -- look at me --
再次踏足塞勒姆
ever return at any time,
不管有何原因
for any reason,
你将会再次与我一同面对群众
you will find yourself once again beside me on the common,
你死气沉沉的尸体
your lifeless body dangling
将被挂在处死吊索的尽头
from the wrong end of the hangman's noose.
带走她
Take her.
柯顿
Cotton!
-格里安娜  -柯顿  柯顿
- Gloriana! - Cotton! Cotton!
柯顿  柯顿
Cotton! Cotton!
-格里安娜  -站回去  退后
- Gloriana! -Stand back. Stay back.
不要  格里安娜
No! Gloriana!
对不起
I'm sorry.
带她到马匹所能及的最远之处
Take her as far as your steeds will travel.
让所有人都知道
And let it be known
不管罪恶还是罪人
neither sin nor sinner
在塞勒姆都没有栖身之地
have any place in Salem.
乔治
George.
我不知道为何或是被谁
I don't know how or by whom,
但是灵兽已经从他身上驱逐
but the familiar has been excised from him.
他可能在任何地方  与任何人交谈
He could be anywhere right now, talking to anyone.
我们所有的努力
All that we've worked for,
所有的牺牲  都在一瞬间灰飞烟灭
all that I've sacrificed, incinerated in an instant.
冷静下来  然后来帮我
Calm yourself and help me.
变化  洞悉的力量[拉丁语]
Mutare, et notum sumbotis.
展现出身形[拉丁语]
Forma enim esse ostendit.
身体  灵魂  思想[拉丁语]
Corpus, anima, mens.
引领我至我寻找之人
Lead me to the one I seek.
此物将引领我找到他
The creature will lead me to him.
如果幸运  我很快就会找到他
With luck, I will find him quickly.
如果没有  我们都会被烧死
And without it, we shall all burn.
你对我的处理方法有意见
You take issue with my methods.
我理解
I understand.
你需要理解的是  我所做的一切
What you need to understand is that everything I have done
都是为了能让你承担起麦哲之名
has been to make you worthy of the Mather name.
我爱她
I loved her.
不许你这么说
Do not say that.
就算沉默也不代表这不是真的
My silence does not make it untrue.
总有一天
One day,
当你成为这片伟大土地的统治者
when you are governor of this great land,
一个手握重权的道德楷模
a man of power and a model of virtue,
被敬爱的同时又被畏惧着
respected and feared in equal measure,
你会回想起这一天
you will trace it back to this day...
我将诱惑从你面前驱走的那一天
...the day I removed temptation from your path.
-那个你  -是的
- You there. - Yes?
给我上点红茶  很浓的  谢谢
Bring me some black tea, very strong, if you please.
你不是那个昨天负责将
Are you not the young man
西布里先生送到波士顿的年轻人吗
who transported Mr. Sibley to Boston yesterday?
我叫艾萨克  先生
Isaac, sir.
-艾萨克  -是的
- Issac. - Mm.
你从波士顿回来了
Boston and back?
真是迅速
Record time.
你一定是个技艺高超的车夫  艾萨克
You must be quite the horseman, Isaac.
不  我可不这么认为
No, I-I wouldn't say that.
跟我说说
Well, tell me.
那里的医师对先生的病情
Did the physician offer any insight
看法如何
into the patient's condition?
医师
Physician?
有任何诊断和结论吗
A diagnosis? Or a prognosis?
我不...
No, I can't...
你确实带西布里先生去了医院  对吧
Well, you did take Mr. Sibley to the hospital, did you not?
有什么是你没告诉我的
What is it you are not saying?
艾萨克  看着我
Isaac...look at me.
你们在路上到底发生了什么事
Tell me the truth about your journey.
伤者朝着内陆南行
The injured is due south, inland,
在去往波士顿的林路上
on the wooded path to Boston.
别挡道
Clear the way.
是谁  快现身
Who's there? Show yourself.
你是谁
Who are you?
我是彼得鲁斯
The name is Petrus.
一小时前  我发现您昏睡在这里
Not an hour ago, I spied you sleeping,
而且深受重伤  我便去拿了点药回来
and, seeing your grave wound, I have returned with medicinals.
别过来  理我远点
Stop. Not one step closer.
可是先生  你的伤口已经感染了
But, sir, an infection has already taken root.
不劳你费心  已经有人赶来救我了
Do not worry yourself. Aid is on the way.
但您很痛苦  不是吗
But you are in pain, are you not?
我调配了些简单的药剂
I have concocted a simple physic
用以减轻您的痛苦
to ease your suffering.
芸芸众生  无论贵贱
No creature, man or animal,
都不该遭受您这样的痛苦  先生
should suffer as you do, sir.
喝点吧
Please.
你给我喝的是什么
What have you given me?
真的很抱歉  先生
I am truly sorry, sir.
是她逼我这么做的
She made me.
把他带去你的窝棚避避风声
We will take him to your shack
直到威胁解除
until the threat has passed.
你真的以为能如此轻易地
Did you really think it would be so easy
逃离我们吗  西布里先生
to escape us, Mr. Sibley?
那边  就在前面
There, up ahead!
乔治  乔治
George? George?
你是他们家的仆人
You're the servant?
是的  先生  西布里太太
Yes, sir, sent by Mrs. Sibley
派我来带回她病重的丈夫
to retrieve her ailing husband.
这比我想象的更严重
This is worse than I had feared.
所以我们要将他立刻送去医院接受治疗
Which is why he needs to be taken to hospital at once.
不
No.
我担心的不是伤势
It is not the injury that troubles me,
而是他的伤是怎么来的
but how he came by it.
看上去他像是为了挣脱巫师对他的控制
He sought to free himself from the witches' grip.
我不明白你的意思
I do not understand.
他不是有病
The man is not ill.
是被下咒了
He has been spelled.
难道你对此一无所知吗
Might you know something about that?
霍尔小姐
Miss Hale.
你还记得那天下午在墓地  你暗示过我
Do you remember that afternoon in the graveyard,
说我父亲并不像表面看起来如此简单吗
when you implied my father is not who he seems?
记得
Yes.
请我进去  我就告诉你为什么我同意你的看法
Invite me inside, and I'll tell you why I agree.
告诉我  西布里先生在哪
Tell me -- where is Mr. Sibley?
我们有麻烦了
We have a problem.
你没回答我的问题
That was not my question.
你到底知不知道他在哪里
Either you know where he is, or you don't.
我确实知道他的下落
I do know where he is,
这就是麻烦所在
and that is the problem.
牧师认为乔治是巫术的受害者
The reverend has deemed him a victim of witchcraft
因此决定他将亲自照料乔治
and has decided that George is to rest under his care.
都快点  赶紧的
Quickly now. Make haste.
我的上帝
My god.
彼得鲁斯的药效只能持续一天
Petrus' physic will last but a day.
就是这样  快到了
There. There.
然后西布里先生即将恢复神智  迫不及待地
And then Mr. Sibley will awake, lucid and eager.
将一切向英克里斯全盘托出
to tell Increase everything.